{
    "subject": "resource/Jeff_Panzer_(ice_hockey)",
    "predicate": "ontology/formerTeam",
    "object": "resource/Rapperswil-Jona_Lakers",
    "human_readable": "Jeff Panzer (ice hockey) used to play for Rapperswil-Jona Lakers.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9749518036842346,
            "question": "Who played ice hockey for Rapperswil-Jona Lakers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9642118215560913,
            "question": "Has Jeff Panzer ever played for the Rapperswil-Jona Lakers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9298740029335022,
            "question": "Who played for Rapperswil-Jona Lakers?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.849532961845398,
            "question": "Is Jeff Panzer associated with ice hockey?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8429830074310303,
            "question": "For which team did Jeff Panzer used to play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7453399896621704,
            "question": "What team is Rapperswil-Jona Lakers affiliated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7281010746955872,
            "question": "What sport did Jeff Panzer play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6229500770568848,
            "question": "Name a former team of Jeff Panzer."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.535721480846405,
            "question": "What team was Jeff Panzer associated with in his career?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5154336094856262,
            "question": "Jeff Panzer's profession is related to which sport?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Jeff Panzer (ice hockey) used to play for Rapperswil-Jona Lakers.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3530_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What team was Jeff Panzer associated with in his career?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3530_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name a former team of Jeff Panzer.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3530_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What sport did Jeff Panzer play?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3530_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3530_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3530_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3530_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3530_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3530_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3530_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3530_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3530_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3530_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3530_6.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can confirm that:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason is that according to the documents, Jeff Panzer played for the Grand Rapids Griffins, Syracuse Crunch, and Worcester IceCats in the American Hockey League (AHL), as well as the Rapperswil-Jona Lakers in the National League A (NLA) and the DEL, but there's no mention of him playing for the Rapperswil-Jona Lakers specifically."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Jeff Panzer played professionally and were associated with the Rapperswil-Jona Lakers, which is a professional ice hockey club. Therefore, it supports the statement that Jeff Panzer used to play for the Rapperswil-Jona Lakers."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "Jeff Panzer played for Rapperswil-Jona Lakers during his professional ice hockey career, which was a different team than SC Rapperswil-Jona Lakers, they are the same team but have changed their name twice.",
            "category": 1
        }
    }
}